Bikram Karki

ERP Engineer & Linux System Administrator

Baniyatar, Gongabu Kathmandu

Ph: 9843782457 | 9818988438 Email: bkarki187@gmail.com bikramk7@protonmail.com

Skills

A Linux System Admin and ERP Engineer with experience on various Linux servers like CentOS 7, Debian, Ubuntu and cloud providers like AWS, Software Planning and Requirement Analysis, Software Programming(Python) and Software Delivery, working on an ERP firm. Experienced on

- Agile methodology of software planning and development,
- Software Planning and Requirement Analysis,
- Project Management and Software Delivery,
- GNU/Linux OSs and Open Source,
- Computer Software Programming(Framework: Odoo,Django; Language: Python, JS, Bootstrap/CSS),
- MVC Architecture of Software Development
- Containerization platforms like LXC, Docker,
- Orchestrators like Docker Swarm,
- Database Management and Administration(PostgreSQL),
- VCS like GIT.
- VOIP(Asterisk) and SIP Configuration

Experience

10 Orbits Pvt. Ltd. / ERP Engineer & Project Manager

MAY, 2019 - PRESENT, Bakhundole, Lalitpur

ERP Engineer with responsibilities of Requirement Analysis, Software Development, Software Project Management, Software Delivery and Implementation.

System Administrator For Linux Servers

BI Solutions Pvt Ltd. / ERP Developer & System Admin

AUGUST, 2017 - NOVEMBER, 2018, Kumaripati, Lalitpur

ERP Developer with responsibilities of developing modules on Python, Developing Database Schemas.

System Administrator For Linux Servers and Database Administrator(PostgreSQL)

Education

Amrit Campus(ASCOL) / B.Sc. CSIT

2015 - 2019, Lainchaur, Kathmandu

Aggregate: 76.11%

Morgan International College / +2 Science

2012 - 2014, Basundhara, Kathmandu

Aggregate: 73%

Future Star English HSS / SLC

2010 - 2012, Sundarbajar, Lamjung

Aggregate: 82.38%

Language

English

Writing, Speaking, Listening

Proficient in Written and Verbal Communication with good communication Skills

Nepali

Writing, Speaking, Listening

Proficient in Written and Verbal Communication with good communication Skills